<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>handynaijaadmin &#8211; Handynaija &#8211; Nigeria&#039;s Largest Hub of Service Providers</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 10:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>./../../../wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-Favicon-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>handynaijaadmin &#8211; Handynaija &#8211; Nigeria&#039;s Largest Hub of Service Providers</title>
	<link>./../../../</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>./../../../2020/05/02/hello-world/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2020/05/02/hello-world/index.html#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 17:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2020/05/02/hello-world/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coupon for Samsung TV give 10%</title>
		<link>./../../../2019/07/19/coupon-for-lg-phones-give-10/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2019/07/19/coupon-for-lg-phones-give-10/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2019 12:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coupons and deals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://recart.wpsoul.com/?p=1350</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every hour, one lucky customer will get 100% cashback on Delhi metro card recharge. Promocode can only be used once per card number. Promocode can be used 3 times per user. Cashback is credited within 24 hours of the transaction into user’s Paytm Wallet. How to use Coupon functions of Rehub]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul><li>Every hour, one lucky customer will get 100% cashback on Delhi metro card recharge.</li><li>Promocode can only be used once per card number.</li><li>Promocode can be used 3 times per user.</li><li>Cashback is credited within 24 hours of the transaction into user’s Paytm Wallet.</li></ul>



<p><a href="http://rehubdocs.wpsoul.com/docs/rehub-theme/affiliate-settings/coupon-functions/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to use Coupon functions of Rehub</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2019/07/19/coupon-for-lg-phones-give-10/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sticky AutoContents Panel</title>
		<link>./../../../2019/06/30/sticky-autocontents-panel/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2019/06/30/sticky-autocontents-panel/index.html#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 15:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://recart.wpsoul.com/?p=1017</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the GoPro Hero5 has many of the same specs as the previous generation when it comes to video and photo resolutions, there are some new features in it.&#160; Individually no single feature is a massive leap forward in the action cam industry, but collectively they represent a notable and substantial difference over the Hero4 [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="content-sticky-panel"><span id="mobileactivate"><i class="fas fa-ellipsis-v" aria-hidden="true"></i></span></div>


<div class="wpsm_update mobfont90"><span class="label-info">Update - 2018.01.27</span>This is &#8220;Offer and Review Score&#8221; Post Layout. You can also add sticky contents panel</div>



<p>While the GoPro Hero5 has many of the same specs as the previous generation when it comes to video and photo resolutions, there are some new features in it.&nbsp; Individually no single feature is a massive leap forward in the action cam industry, but collectively they represent a notable and substantial difference over the Hero4 Black.&nbsp; This section is mostly focused on these new features, while the remaining sections take a deeper dive into the core functions of the camera, as well as touch on these new features in more detail.</p>



<p>Fully Waterproofed: Probably the most notable item is that the GoPro Hero5 Black is now fully waterproofed without the need for a separate case, just like the GoPro Hero4 Session was.&nbsp; In fact, it has nearly the same rubberish material on the outside.</p>



<p>What is of more concern though is the USB-C/HDMI port door.&nbsp; This door pops off for placement into the Karma gimbal/drone, as well as just for charging:</p>



<h2>Deals</h2>


<div class="wpsm-titlebox wpsm_style_1"><strong class="">Gopro 7 deals</strong><div>

</div></div>



<p>Now this won’t easily pop-off while it’s locked in place, as you have to press a button down to open it (plus slide it).&nbsp; But, the trick will be not losing it after charging your camera or while the charging cable is attached.&nbsp; GoPro does sell the door as an accessory (albeit over priced), and I know I plan to buy an extra door and then seal it up somewhere special in my backpack/suitcase for traveling.&nbsp; Because I guarantee you that I’ll lose it at the most inopportune time on a trip to some beautiful watery location and be unable to take pictures of The Girl underwater in a bikini without the door.</p>



<p>Speaking of doors that we don’t want opening up, we’ve also got the battery compartment down below.&nbsp; That holds both the battery as well as the micro-SD card:</p>



<h2>Touch Display:</h2>



<p>The Hero5 takes the touch display found on the Hero4 Silver and advanced it forward.&nbsp; As you might remember, the Hero4 Black actually lacked a display.&nbsp; This was one reason that the Hero4 Silver was actually a more day to day favorite of mine than the Hero4 Black was.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-style-large"><p>However, the touch display acts and feels significantly different here than the Hero7 Silver.</p></blockquote>



<p>The entire menu system has been redone to make it more intuitive to find settings.&nbsp; Along the bottom it shows you the basics for that mode.&nbsp; For example, in the video mode it shows you resolution and frame rate.</p>



<p>You can tap on it to change these specs.&nbsp; Only the available frame rates will display for a given resolution.&nbsp; In theory this looks beautiful, but in practice it’s actually more cumbersome than I expected.&nbsp; I think this is because there’s just too many resolutions too closely together for a normal sized finger to hit the right resolution on that small display.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://recart.wpsoul.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/middle-1024x248.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-503"/></figure>



<p>On the right side of the display you can enable various advanced settings for that mode, such as ProTune, Image Stabilization, and Audio Control:</p>


<hr class="wpsm-divider dotted_divider" style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />


<span class="wpsm-highlight wpsm-highlight-yellow">All of this is of course waterproof as well.&nbsp; Though, it won’t work underwater.&nbsp; For that you’ll need to use the push-buttons on the top/side of the camera to change modes. </span>


<hr class="wpsm-divider dotted_divider" style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />



<p>Speaking of a wet display, in general I found it doesn’t work well when wet either.&nbsp; Especially if your fingers are wet, it all goes to crap and fails to respond.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="alignright is-resized"><img src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiback.png" alt="" class="wp-image-698" width="283" height="233" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiback.png 350w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiback-599x493.png 599w" sizes="(max-width: 283px) 100vw, 283px" /></figure></div>



<p>You can turn this option on/off, and it’s available in seven languages.&nbsp; Also, if you have the Remo accessory remote, that’ll accept voice commands too in the event the camera is out of range of your voice.</p>



<p>But…it’s not perfect.&nbsp; I found that it works most of the time when standing still.&nbsp; But once you start moving I found both it and the Hero5 Session actually perform worse than Garmin does.&nbsp; At about 10MPH (15KPH) I find the ability to give commands pretty much dies no matter which way the camera is facing.&nbsp; Whereas with Garmin it’ll continue working above that speed as long as the camera is facing you.</p>



<h2>Video &amp; Audio details</h2>



<p>Ahh yes, video time.&nbsp; No better place to start diving into features than video modes.&nbsp; In many ways the Hero5 is similar in these modes to the Hero4 Black.&nbsp; After all, it too has 4K @ 30FPS and 720P @ 240FPS, the two ends of the spectrum that people often talk about.&nbsp; The footage looks beautiful in 4K – no doubt.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="GoPro HERO5 IN-DEPTH! Hands-on!" width="840" height="473" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vvCuYUMzjyk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>So what’s new and notable here?&nbsp; Well we’ll start with the video stabilization.&nbsp; Technically this is ‘electronic image stabilization’, which works by taking a larger resolution video clip (i.e. 4K) and then smoothing the video by offering a reduced resolution rate while stabilized (up to 2.7K).&nbsp; By doing this it essentially stabilizes by cutting the edges off the corners to make the video appear smooth.&nbsp; It’s the same thing that Garmin does on their VIRB Ultra 30 (but the Garmin is limited to 1440 vs the higher 2.7K), but is different than what Sony does with their new X3000R, where they use optical image stabilization.&nbsp; That’s better because it doesn’t crop any of the image.</p>


<hr class="wpsm-divider dotted_divider" style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />


<span class="wpsm-highlight wpsm-highlight-blue">To enable image stabilization, you’ll simply swipe from the right.&nbsp; It’ll warn you about cutting about 10% of the field of view:</span>


<hr class="wpsm-divider dotted_divider" style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />



<p>For cases where you’ve got some light chop in the roadway, or even for hand holding the unit, image stabilization can dramatically improve things.&nbsp; Though, that’s at the sacrifice of resolution.&nbsp; If your final output product’s 1080p, then it’s largely a no-brainer.&nbsp; Do note that it generally works better when you’re shooting something that has a large portion of the image facing one direction constantly.&nbsp; Versus on a helmet mount, it can get a bit wonky as you move the view around a bunch.</p>



<p>What’s even more interesting though is the ability to record the native audio files from each microphone separately.&nbsp; If you enable ProTune, you’ll see a new option to do this.&nbsp; Within that you have three levels:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://recart.wpsoul.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/photosplash-e1561583838398-1024x450.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-779"/></figure>



<p>All of these were simply taken at room temperature; obviously aspects like environmental temperature will impact things considerably, as will other modes and increased frame rates.&nbsp; But those give you some basic bounds to work within.</p>



<h2>Photo mode:</h2>



<p>While the Hero7 Black doesn’t offer any more resolution than the Hero4 Black did, it does offer a number of substantial photo-focused features.&nbsp; First, the basics though.&nbsp; To get into the photo mode you’ll go ahead and tap the mode button until you see photos.&nbsp; Or, just tell the GoPro to take a photo using voice commands.</p>



<p>Now there are technically different photo modes, including the ability to take a burst photo, a series of photos as a timelapse, or night photos. Note that this photo timelapse is separate from the video timelapse option.&nbsp; This produces a crapton of photo files, whereas the video timelapse produces a single video timelapse file.</p>



<p>That’s the basic differences. Again, both cameras are very good, you won’t go wrong with either.&nbsp; For me, I prefer the Hero5 Black because I like to be able to see and frame up what I’m taking a photo/video of.&nbsp; Whereas the Hero5 Session it’s shoot and pray that you’ve got it lined up.&nbsp; Sure, you can use your phone for certain shots – but most of us won’t do that.</p>



<h2>Our score</h2>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2019/06/30/sticky-autocontents-panel/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scorebox in sidebar</title>
		<link>./../../../2019/06/30/scorebox-in-sidebar/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2019/06/30/scorebox-in-sidebar/index.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 15:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://recart.wpsoul.com/?p=1014</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It has introduced a new storage option though, with a 32GB model now lining up alongside the 128GB 6S Plus. The 32GB variant will set you back $649 (£599, AU$1,079) &#8211; which is cheaper than the launch price for the now discontinued 16GB phone. The 128GB model – which we tried out for this review [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="mb30 wpsm_box blue_type nonefloat_box" style="text-align:left; width:auto"><i></i><div>
			This is example of scorebox shortcode in widget. You can <a href="http://rehub.wpsoul.com/documentation/docs.html#scorebox" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">find parameters here</a>

			</div></div>



<p>It has introduced a new storage option though, with a 32GB model now lining up alongside the 128GB 6S Plus. The 32GB variant will set you back $649 (£599, AU$1,079) &#8211; which is cheaper than the launch price for the now discontinued 16GB phone.</p>



<p>The 128GB model – which we tried out for this review – launched at $949 (£789, AU$1,529), but can now be had for $749 (£699, AU$1,229). The good news in the US is that the phone does come unlocked at these prices and works on any carrier, GSMA or CDMA.</p>



<h2>Design</h2>



<p>There&#8217;s no mistaking the incremental credentials of the phone&nbsp;when it comes to design. It looks identical to the phone, and I mean identical.</p>



<p>In fact, the only obvious marking that differentiates the 6S is the small &#8216;S&#8217; logo on the rear below the word &#8216;Phone&#8217; – although it will be covered by your hand 90% of the time (or 100% of the time by a case).</p>



<p>The sleek, rounded metal body continues to look and feel premium, with the build quality you&#8217;d expect from gader. After last year&#8217;s unfortunate &#8216;bendgate&#8217; fiasco, Gator&nbsp;has looked to reassure people that its latest smartphone duo are tough. This isn&#8217;t strictly necessary, given that we&#8217;d have expected last year&#8217;s models to be strong enough to get through a couple of years of use, but some clarification was needed.</p>



<p>The familiar design of the Phone &nbsp;Plus will be comforting to the faithful, while outsiders may look on with raised eyebrows, mumbling something about a lack of progression from the Cupertino firm. And they may have a point.</p>



<h2>Design and Handling</h2>



<p>On first viewing the screen on the Phone &nbsp;is the same as its predecessor, with the 5.5-inch panel sporting a full HD resolution and 401ppi pixel density.</p>



<p>The IPS screen is covered in toughened glass with fingerprint-resistant oleophobic coating, and it does a better job than most at keeping the display relatively print-free.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Hold the Phone &nbsp;side by side to the Phone 6 &nbsp;and there are no visible differences between the two</p><cite>Eric Nightman</cite></blockquote>



<p>Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec quam felis, ultricies nec, pellentesque eu, pretium quis, sem. Nulla consequat massa quis enim. Donec pede justo, fringilla vel, aliquet nec, vulputate eget, arcu. In enim justo, rhoncus ut, imperdiet a, venenatis vitae, justo. Nullam dictum felis eu pede mollis pretium.<span id="more-44"></span></p>



<h2>Screen and EVF</h2>



<p>Sed consequat, leo eget bibendum sodales, augue velit cursus nunc, quis gravida magna mi a libero. Fusce vulputate eleifend sapien. Vestibulum purus quam, scelerisque ut, mollis sed, nonummy id, metus. Nullam accumsan lorem in dui. Cras ultricies mi eu turpis hendrerit fringilla. Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia Curae; In ac dui quis mi consectetuer lacinia. Nam pretium turpis et arcu. Duis arcu tortor, suscipit eget, imperdiet nec, imperdiet iaculis, ipsum.</p>


<div class="mb30 wpsm_box info_type nonefloat_box" style="text-align:left; width:auto"><i></i><div>
			
Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec quam felis, ultricies nec, pellentesque eu, pretium quis, sem. Nulla consequat massa quis enim. Donec pede justo, fringilla vel, aliquet nec, vulputate eget, arcu. In enim justo, rhoncus ut, imperdiet a, venenatis vitae, justo. Nullam dictum felis eu pede mollis pretium.

			</div></div>



<p>Integer tincidunt. Cras dapibus. Vivamus elementum semper nisi. Aenean vulputate eleifend tellus. Aenean leo ligula, porttitor eu, consequat vitae, eleifend ac, enim. Aliquam lorem ante, dapibus in, viverra quis, feugiat a, tellus. Phasellus viverra nulla ut metus varius laoreet. Quisque rutrum. Aenean imperdiet. Etiam ultricies nisi vel augue. Curabitur ullamcorper ultricies nisi. Nam eget dui. Etiam rhoncus.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2019/06/30/scorebox-in-sidebar/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Example of AutoContent List and Review</title>
		<link>./../../../2019/06/30/example-of-autocontent-list-and-review/index.html</link>
					<comments>./../../../2019/06/30/example-of-autocontent-list-and-review/index.html#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 15:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://recart.wpsoul.com/?p=1007</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[While the GoPro Hero5 has many of the same specs as the previous generation when it comes to video and photo resolutions, there are some new features in it.&#160; Individually no single feature is a massive leap forward in the action cam industry, but collectively they represent a notable and substantial difference over the Hero4 [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="wpsm_update mobfont90"><span class="label-info">Update - 2018.01.27</span>This is &#8220;Title outside Content&#8221; Post Layout. You can also <a href="http://rehubdocs.wpsoul.com/docs/rehub-theme/how-to/how-to-make-auto-contents-for-post/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">add sticky contents panel</a></div>


<p></p>



<p>While the GoPro Hero5 has many of the same specs as the previous generation when it comes to video and photo resolutions, there are some new features in it.&nbsp; Individually no single feature is a massive leap forward in the action cam industry, but collectively they represent a notable and substantial difference over the Hero4 Black.&nbsp; This section is mostly focused on these new features, while the remaining sections take a deeper dive into the core functions of the camera, as well as touch on these new features in more detail.</p>



<p>Fully Waterproofed: Probably the most notable item is that the GoPro Hero5 Black is now fully waterproofed without the need for a separate case, just like the GoPro Hero4 Session was.&nbsp; In fact, it has nearly the same rubberish material on the outside.</p>



<p>What is of more concern though is the USB-C/HDMI port door.&nbsp; This door pops off for placement into the Karma gimbal/drone, as well as just for charging:</p>



<h2>Deals</h2>


<div class="wpsm-titlebox wpsm_style_1"><strong class="">Gopro 7 deals</strong><div>

</div></div>



<p>Now this won’t easily pop-off while it’s locked in place, as you have to press a button down to open it (plus slide it).&nbsp; But, the trick will be not losing it after charging your camera or while the charging cable is attached.&nbsp; GoPro does sell the door as an accessory (albeit over priced), and I know I plan to buy an extra door and then seal it up somewhere special in my backpack/suitcase for traveling.&nbsp; Because I guarantee you that I’ll lose it at the most inopportune time on a trip to some beautiful watery location and be unable to take pictures of The Girl underwater in a bikini without the door.</p>



<p>Speaking of doors that we don’t want opening up, we’ve also got the battery compartment down below.&nbsp; That holds both the battery as well as the micro-SD card:</p>



<h2>Touch Display:</h2>



<p>The Hero5 takes the touch display found on the Hero4 Silver and advanced it forward.&nbsp; As you might remember, the Hero4 Black actually lacked a display.&nbsp; This was one reason that the Hero4 Silver was actually a more day to day favorite of mine than the Hero4 Black was.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-style-large"><p>However, the touch display acts and feels significantly different here than the Hero7 Silver.</p></blockquote>



<p>The entire menu system has been redone to make it more intuitive to find settings.&nbsp; Along the bottom it shows you the basics for that mode.&nbsp; For example, in the video mode it shows you resolution and frame rate.</p>



<p>You can tap on it to change these specs.&nbsp; Only the available frame rates will display for a given resolution.&nbsp; In theory this looks beautiful, but in practice it’s actually more cumbersome than I expected.&nbsp; I think this is because there’s just too many resolutions too closely together for a normal sized finger to hit the right resolution on that small display.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://recart.wpsoul.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/middle-1024x248.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-503"/></figure>



<p>On the right side of the display you can enable various advanced settings for that mode, such as ProTune, Image Stabilization, and Audio Control:</p>


<hr class="wpsm-divider dotted_divider" style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />


<span class="wpsm-highlight wpsm-highlight-yellow">All of this is of course waterproof as well.&nbsp; Though, it won’t work underwater.&nbsp; For that you’ll need to use the push-buttons on the top/side of the camera to change modes. </span>


<hr class="wpsm-divider dotted_divider" style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />



<p>Speaking of a wet display, in general I found it doesn’t work well when wet either.&nbsp; Especially if your fingers are wet, it all goes to crap and fails to respond.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="alignright is-resized"><img src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiback.png" alt="" class="wp-image-698" width="283" height="233" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiback.png 350w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiback-599x493.png 599w" sizes="(max-width: 283px) 100vw, 283px" /></figure></div>



<p>You can turn this option on/off, and it’s available in seven languages.&nbsp; Also, if you have the Remo accessory remote, that’ll accept voice commands too in the event the camera is out of range of your voice.</p>



<p>But…it’s not perfect.&nbsp; I found that it works most of the time when standing still.&nbsp; But once you start moving I found both it and the Hero5 Session actually perform worse than Garmin does.&nbsp; At about 10MPH (15KPH) I find the ability to give commands pretty much dies no matter which way the camera is facing.&nbsp; Whereas with Garmin it’ll continue working above that speed as long as the camera is facing you.</p>



<h2>Video &amp; Audio details</h2>



<p>Ahh yes, video time.&nbsp; No better place to start diving into features than video modes.&nbsp; In many ways the Hero5 is similar in these modes to the Hero4 Black.&nbsp; After all, it too has 4K @ 30FPS and 720P @ 240FPS, the two ends of the spectrum that people often talk about.&nbsp; The footage looks beautiful in 4K – no doubt.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="GoPro HERO5 IN-DEPTH! Hands-on!" width="840" height="473" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vvCuYUMzjyk?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>So what’s new and notable here?&nbsp; Well we’ll start with the video stabilization.&nbsp; Technically this is ‘electronic image stabilization’, which works by taking a larger resolution video clip (i.e. 4K) and then smoothing the video by offering a reduced resolution rate while stabilized (up to 2.7K).&nbsp; By doing this it essentially stabilizes by cutting the edges off the corners to make the video appear smooth.&nbsp; It’s the same thing that Garmin does on their VIRB Ultra 30 (but the Garmin is limited to 1440 vs the higher 2.7K), but is different than what Sony does with their new X3000R, where they use optical image stabilization.&nbsp; That’s better because it doesn’t crop any of the image.</p>


<hr class="wpsm-divider dotted_divider" style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />


<span class="wpsm-highlight wpsm-highlight-blue">To enable image stabilization, you’ll simply swipe from the right.&nbsp; It’ll warn you about cutting about 10% of the field of view:</span>


<hr class="wpsm-divider dotted_divider" style="margin-top: 20px;margin-bottom: 20px;" />



<p>For cases where you’ve got some light chop in the roadway, or even for hand holding the unit, image stabilization can dramatically improve things.&nbsp; Though, that’s at the sacrifice of resolution.&nbsp; If your final output product’s 1080p, then it’s largely a no-brainer.&nbsp; Do note that it generally works better when you’re shooting something that has a large portion of the image facing one direction constantly.&nbsp; Versus on a helmet mount, it can get a bit wonky as you move the view around a bunch.</p>



<p>What’s even more interesting though is the ability to record the native audio files from each microphone separately.&nbsp; If you enable ProTune, you’ll see a new option to do this.&nbsp; Within that you have three levels:</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://recart.wpsoul.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/photosplash-e1561583838398-1024x450.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-779"/></figure>



<p>All of these were simply taken at room temperature; obviously aspects like environmental temperature will impact things considerably, as will other modes and increased frame rates.&nbsp; But those give you some basic bounds to work within.</p>



<h2>Photo mode:</h2>



<p>While the Hero7 Black doesn’t offer any more resolution than the Hero4 Black did, it does offer a number of substantial photo-focused features.&nbsp; First, the basics though.&nbsp; To get into the photo mode you’ll go ahead and tap the mode button until you see photos.&nbsp; Or, just tell the GoPro to take a photo using voice commands.</p>



<p>Now there are technically different photo modes, including the ability to take a burst photo, a series of photos as a timelapse, or night photos. Note that this photo timelapse is separate from the video timelapse option.&nbsp; This produces a crapton of photo files, whereas the video timelapse produces a single video timelapse file.</p>



<p>That’s the basic differences. Again, both cameras are very good, you won’t go wrong with either.&nbsp; For me, I prefer the Hero5 Black because I like to be able to see and frame up what I’m taking a photo/video of.&nbsp; Whereas the Hero5 Session it’s shoot and pray that you’ve got it lined up.&nbsp; Sure, you can use your phone for certain shots – but most of us won’t do that.</p>



<h2>Our score</h2>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>./../../../2019/06/30/example-of-autocontent-list-and-review/feed/index.html</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elementor and Content Egg Offer Modules</title>
		<link>./../../../2019/06/30/set-of-coupons/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 14:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://recart.wpsoul.com/?p=996</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[All these Blocks are added via Elementor in Frontend Editing. You can add such blocks manually or import Data from Products (just type name of product which you want to import) -50% Best deal Phone Offers ★★★★★ $11.99 $22.11 Starting from purchases $200 Check this offer AWESOME166 days left This is Big Offer Block made [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="996" class="elementor elementor-996" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section class="elementor-element elementor-element-2641022 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-id="2641022" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-ffac79e elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-id="ffac79e" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-2394db3 elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="2394db3" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix"><p>All these Blocks are added via Elementor in Frontend Editing. You can add such blocks manually or import Data from Products (just type name of product which you want to import)</p></div>
				</div>
				</div>
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-16b1539 elementor-widget elementor-widget-wpsm-offerbox" data-id="16b1539" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="wpsm-offerbox.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			
    
     
 <div class="bigofferblock pt20 pl20 pr20  expired_coupon">
<div class="col_wrap_two mb0">
    <div class="product_egg">
        <div class="image col_item mobileblockdisplay">
            <a class="re_track_btn" href="http://google.com/">
                <img class="lazyload" data-src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/thumbs_dir/s10-oqderqyqx807mt64a1sz8l02o2t1at1a7v6ab7jhra.jpg" width="500" alt="Best deal Phone Offers" src="./../../../wp-content/themes/rehub-theme/images/default/blank.gif" />                                    <span class="sale_a_proc">
                        -50%                    </span>
                                                   
            </a>                             
        </div>
        <div class="product-summary col_item mobileblockdisplay">         
            <h2 class="product_title entry-title">
                <a class="re_track_btn" href="http://google.com/">
                    Best deal Phone Offers 
                </a>
            </h2>
                            <div class="cegg-rating">
                    <span>&#x2605;</span><span>&#x2605;</span><span>&#x2605;</span><span>&#x2605;</span><span>&#x2605;</span>                </div>   
                        

                            <div class="deal-box-price">
                    $11.99                                        <span class="retail-old">
                      <strike>$22.11</strike>
                    </span>
                                                          
                </div>                
            
                            <div class="rev_disclaimer font70 greencolor lineheight15 mb15">Starting from purchases $200</div>
                        
                                              
            <div class="buttons_col">
                <div class="priced_block clearfix">
                    <div>
                                                    <a class="re_track_btn btn_offer_block" href="http://google.com/">
                                                                    Check this offer                                                            </a> 
                                                                      
                    </div>
                    <div class="rehub_offer_coupon mt15 not_masked_coupon  expired_coupon" data-clipboard-text="AWESOME"><i class="fal fa-cut fa-rotate-180"></i><span class="coupon_text">AWESOME</span></div><div class="time_offer">Expired</div>                    
                </div>                
            </div>   
              
                            <div class="bigofferdesc"><p>This is Big Offer Block made via Elementor. You can have unlimited blocks in posts</p></div>                                                   
                          
        </div>           
    </div> 
</div>
</div>  
<div class="clearfix"></div> 		</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-element elementor-element-8454cd8 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-id="8454cd8" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-00c135a elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-id="00c135a" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-523b5fa elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="523b5fa" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix"><p>Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Ut elit tellus, luctus nec ullamcorper mattis, pulvinar dapibus leo. There are some new features in it.  Individually no single feature is a massive leap forward in the action cam industry, but collectively they represent a notable and substantial difference over the Lorem.  This section is mostly focused on these new features, while the remaining sections take a deeper dive into the core functions of the camera, as well as touch on these new features in more detail.</p></div>
				</div>
				</div>
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-b631126 elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="b631126" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix">Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Ut elit tellus, luctus nec ullamcorper mattis, pulvinar dapibus leo. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Ut elit tellus, luctus nec ullamcorper mattis, pulvinar dapibus leo. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Ut elit tellus, luctus nec ullamcorper mattis, pulvinar dapibus leo.

While the DOLORES has many of the same specs as the previous generation when it comes to video and photo resolutions, there are some new features in it.  Individually no single feature is a massive leap forward in the action cam industry, but collectively they represent a notable and substantial difference over the Lorem.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
				<section class="elementor-element elementor-element-9e59801 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-inner-section" data-id="9e59801" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-eeae59c elementor-column elementor-col-50 elementor-inner-column" data-id="eeae59c" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-38f2145 elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-id="38f2145" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="450" height="365" src="./../../../wp-content/themes/rehub-theme/images/default/blank.gif" data-src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiosmo.png" class="lazyload attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiosmo.png 450w, ./../../../wp-content/uploads/2019/06/djiosmo-599x486.png 599w" sizes="(max-width: 450px) 100vw, 450px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-bfbf019 elementor-column elementor-col-50 elementor-inner-column" data-id="bfbf019" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-d7ff812 elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="d7ff812" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix">Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Ut elit tellus, luctus nec ullamcorper mattis, pulvinar dapibus leo. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Ut elit tellus, luctus nec ullamcorper mattis, pulvinar dapibus leo. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Ut elit tellus, luctus nec ullamcorper mattis, pulvinar dapibus leo.

While the DOLORES has many of the same specs as the previous generation when it comes to video and photo resolutions, there are some new features in it.  Individually no single feature is a massive leap forward in the action cam industry, but collectively they represent a notable and substantial difference over the Lorem.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Win 100% Cashback Every Hour on Delhi Metro Card Recharge</title>
		<link>./../../../2019/06/30/win-100-cashback-every-hour-on-delhi-metro-card-recharge/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 14:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coupons and deals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://recart.wpsoul.com/?p=994</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Every hour, one lucky customer will get 100% cashback on Delhi metro card recharge. Promocode can only be used once per card number. Promocode can be used 3 times per user. Cashback is credited within 24 hours of the transaction into user’s Paytm Wallet. How to use Coupon functions of Rehub]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul><li>Every hour, one lucky customer will get 100% cashback on Delhi metro card recharge.</li><li>Promocode can only be used once per card number.</li><li>Promocode can be used 3 times per user.</li><li>Cashback is credited within 24 hours of the transaction into user’s Paytm Wallet.</li></ul>



<p><a href="http://rehubdocs.wpsoul.com/docs/rehub-theme/affiliate-settings/coupon-functions/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to use Coupon functions of Rehub</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get flat 25% off on orders of $22 &#038; above on paying with SBI credit</title>
		<link>./../../../2019/06/30/get-flat-25-off-on-orders-of-22-above-on-paying-with-sbi-credit/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 14:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coupons and deals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://recart.wpsoul.com/?p=992</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Get flat 25% off on orders of $1499 &#38; above on paying with SBI credit/debit cards. Maximum discount is $500. Not valid on discounted products. How to use Coupon functions of Rehub]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ul><li>Get flat 25% off on orders of $1499 &amp; above on paying with SBI credit/debit cards.</li><li>Maximum discount is $500.</li><li>Not valid on discounted products.</li></ul>



<p><a href="http://rehubdocs.wpsoul.com/docs/rehub-theme/affiliate-settings/coupon-functions/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to use Coupon functions of Rehub</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upto 75% Off on Everyday Essentials</title>
		<link>./../../../2019/06/30/upto-75-off-on-everyday-essentials/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[handynaijaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 14:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coupons and deals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://recart.wpsoul.com/?p=990</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Upto 75% off on everyday essentials. Get discounts on dry fruits, sweets, namkeen, chocolates, snacks, gourmet and on Toys &#38; Games, Baby products, Beauty, Personal Care &#38; Health Appliances, Grocery &#38; Gourmet Foods, Pet Supplies and Health &#38; Personal Care. How to use Coupon Functions of Theme]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<ol><li>Upto 75% off on everyday essentials.</li><li>Get discounts on dry fruits, sweets, namkeen, chocolates, snacks, gourmet and on Toys &amp; Games, Baby products, Beauty, Personal Care &amp; Health Appliances, Grocery &amp; Gourmet Foods, Pet Supplies and Health &amp; Personal Care.</li></ol>



<p><a href="http://rehubdocs.wpsoul.com/docs/rehub-theme/affiliate-settings/coupon-functions/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">How to use Coupon Functions of Theme</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
